// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Based on land size, what is the 2nd largest country in the world?', 
      a: 'Canada', 
      b: 'China',
      c: 'United States',
      d: 'Australia',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many types of Spaniels are recognized by the American Kennel Club?', 
      a: '9', 
      b: '12',
      c: '15',
      d: '18',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of Jane\'s cat?', 
      a: 'Fluffy', 
      b: 'Bella',
      c: 'Jack Ass',
      d: 'Stella',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of Sarah Santa Cruz\'s fluffy cat?', 
      a: 'Chloe', 
      b: 'Fluffy',
      c: 'Zoey',
      d: 'Mrs. Fluffington',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Penn Field was built during which war?', 
      a: 'Civil War', 
      b: 'World War I',
      c: 'World War II',
      d: 'Korean War',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What country has the longest coastline?', 
      a: 'Canada', 
      b: 'Norway',
      c: 'Australia',
      d: 'United States',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following groups of Clearheaders contains all people that have been public school teachers?', 
      a: 'Kendra, John, Joelle, Andrew', 
      b: 'Sarah SC, Devon, Kendra, John',
      c: 'Andrew, Devon, John, Sarah SC',
      d: 'John, Sarah SC, Sarah G, Kendra',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the tallest building in the World?', 
      a: 'Burj Khalifa', 
      b: 'Willis Tower',
      c: 'Shanghai Tower',
      d: 'Entisar Tower',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the final season of Seinfeld, Jerry Seinfeld earned roughly how much money per line?', 
      a: '$8,000', 
      b: '$7,000',
      c: '$25,000',
      d: '$13,000',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Roughly how much did Michael Richards (Kramer) make per line in the final season of Seinfeld?', 
      a: '$4,000', 
      b: '$5,000',
      c: '$12,000',
      d: '$15,000',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};